Jalina Castillo

Sales Producer - Allstate Insurance

Orlando, FL 32809

jalinacastillo8_pov@indeedemail.com - (407) 985-0381

Highly motivated individual with over 9 years of experience in management, customer service & sales. Wide work history, which enables me to both embrace and appreciate an extensive work environment. Adapts to frequent changes to processes in the work place while keeping a keen eye on detail & professionalism. Able to work in both a team and a self-directed environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Producer

Allstate Insurance -

2017 - Present

- Verify Eligibility For Policies
- Write All New Business Lines
- Review & Collect outstanding balances
- Audit All Billing Reports
- Train New Team Members
- Verify Insurance & Coverages
- Customer Service
- Service All Financial Products Lines
- Service All Commercial Auto
- Multi-Line Existing Households
- Market To Local Residents
- Complete Remittance & End Of Day Deposit Report

Team Leader / Sales Representative

State Farm Insurance -

2014 - 2017

- Multi-Line Existing Households
- Verify Eligibility For Products
- Write All New Business Lines
- Audit Billing Reports
- Interview Potential Team Members
- Train New Team Members
- Collect Outstanding Payments
- Process Daily Sales & Endorsement Reports
- Payroll
- Customer Service
- Retain Potential Cancellations
- End Of Day Deposit Report

Licensed Representative

Martell INS Agency -

2006 - 2014

- Writing New Policies Auto, Home, Boat, Motorcycle, Etc.
- Policy Renewal Reviews
- Customer Service
- Payroll
- Train New Hires
- Collect payments
- Complete Remittance Report and Prepare Deposit
- Cross Sell to Existing Clients

Receptionist

Coscan Construction -

2004 - 2006

- Answered calls and transmit to correct department
- Delivered messages in a timely manner
- Filed Documents into proper file
- Kept client records organized

440 & 215 Licensed, References available upon request

EDUCATION

Legal Studies

Keiser University

2013

Medical Assisting

Everest University - Orlando, FL

2009

Diploma in Standard

South Broward High School - Hollywood, FL

2005

SKILLS

BILLING, COLLECTIONS, CREDIT, DATA ENTRY, ETIQUETTE

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills

- Excellent oral communication
- Bilingual
- Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Outlook
- Billing/ Collections
- Data entry/Type 65wpm
- Outstanding phone etiquette